♪ Two... two, three...♪
♪ ♪
Good news, everyone.
Remember when you asked
to see my family tree?
ALL:
No.
Ta-da!
[whirring]
This is my ancestor
Philo Farnsworth,
inventor of television,
and as a bonus,
childhood obesity.
And here'’s Dean Farnsworth,
developer of the Farnsworth Test
for Color-blindness.
Where is he, blast it?!
And just recently, I learned
of a modern-day Farnsworth
who invented
the Anti-Senility Truss.
That'’s you,
Professor.
[mutters]
Ah, yes,
the Farnsworths boast
a proud and
distinguished lineage.
No wormy fruit
on this tree.
What about Fry?
Isn'’t he your
distant uncle?[snoring]
Very distant.
Not a true Farnsworth, mind you.
He'’s way over here
on this filthy branch
riddled with fungus
and dung beetles.
[snoring]
[snoring, gasps]
What'’s with the
17 dung beetles?
Well, it'’s 6:00.
I guess we'’ll have to deliver
that human heart tomorrow.
Good work, people.[whooping]
Time to go clubbing!
Baby seals, here I come.
[sighs]
Guess I better head
over to my night job.
You have a night job?
Yup. It'’s exhausting,
but I need the extra money
to buy coffee
so I can stay awake
for my night job.
But...Got to go!
[crickets chirping]
You'’ve got a surprising
amount of algae
in your beard,
Mr. President.
Just sit still and let the
algae-eater do its work.
Oh! Ow!
Oh! Lay off my trademark mole!
Hi, Lars.
Fry.Whatever.
I'’m heading out
to my night job.
Remember, no loud noise,
no head bowling,
and no parties,
or it'’ll be your ass in a jar.
I want to go to that museum!
[munching]
Man, this place
is a snooze.
Hey, Fry,
I challenge President Taft here
to a pie-eating contest.
You'’re on, skinny.
Sorry, guys.
You know the rules.
No fun allowed.
Come on, you pansy!
I'’m thirsty!
I want me some
Tennessee loopy juice!
And I want
loose women!
The kind that aren'’t afraid
to show a little ankle.
[whispering]:
Or elbow.
No visitors.
I'’ll lose my job.
Oh, boo-hoo,
I'’ll lose my minimum wage job.
[laughter]
You'’re mean,
Rutherford B. Hayes!
Listen here,
young man.
We have nothing
to fear
but running
out of beer.
[sighs]
Oh!
All right, one small
get-together,
but let'’s keep it
quiet and dignified.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. [laughs]
Ooh-wee!
[laughter and whooping]
ALL:
Four more beers!
Yes!
Right in the Ike!
[panting]
Nice elbow action.
So, you grow hemp.
Yes.And, uh, you do
what with it?
All manner of things.
Manufacture paper,
fabric, rope...
Oh. Well, nice
talking to you.
Why, I used to smoke
about four feet of rope a day.
Let me give you
my pager number.
Hey, Reagan, remember when
you asked to see my family tree?
I asked you to
leave me alone.
[whirring]
The Farnsworths
are a remarkable...
Farnsworth?! That name is a
stain on American history.
One of the worst traitors of
the Revolution was a Farnsworth.
You'’re lying!He'’s George
Washington.
He tends not
to do that.
David Farnsworth was a notorious
British agent and counterfeiter.
He conspired
to bring down our nation
with his fraudulent currency!
A Farnsworth did this?
Oh, dear!
My good name is ruined!
Hi. I'’m Jerry.
I like movies.
♪ ♪
Anyone seen
Ulysses Grant?
He owes me a cheroot.
He'’s over there,
puking in the bushes.
BOTH:
No!
[all gasping]
Oh, boy.
Mr. Fry!
Why are all these people
standing around...
when they should be partying?
[cheering]
[dance music playing]
Hey, hey, LBJ,
you want to get drunk?
Oh, hell, yeah.
[grunting]
Zoidberg, no!
The effects
of jar juice
aren'’t fully
understood.
Eh, not bad.
A hint of Vitalis and...
Whoa!
I recognize this.
It'’s the 1960s!
I did a report on it for
my drug-taking class.
Hi, I'’m Andy Warhol,
and you'’re some kind
of marvelous lobster-man.
Right on.
Say, you got any real soup,
or just this schlock?
[whoosh]
What a horrid bore.
Ooh.Huh?
Far out.
That head gave me
a total head trip!
Really? I'’m gonna lick
Herbert Hoover'’s head.
ALL:
Lick the head!
[chiming, whoosh]
Whoa, a
speakeasy!
One prohibited
beverage, please.
Hey, Dutch,
the new still is here!
I'’m not a still. I
just smell like one.
[tires screeching,
police siren wailing]
MAN [with Irish accent]:
Dutch Schultz, come out
with your bootleg whiskey.
We'’re thirsty!
[gunfire]
[gunshot]
[whoosh]
What the heck
is going on?
Jefferson,
did you sell me some bad rope?
It must have something to do
with the jar fluid.
[sniffing]
Aha!
Dr. Cahill, do I detect
a trace of opalescence?
Very observant, Professor.
To preserve the heads,
we use a rare form
of powdered
crystalline opal.
[mechanical rhythmic humming]
This is the world'’s
entire supply.
Yet it'’s so powerful,
it should last a thousand years.
It keeps the heads alive,
but we don'’t know how.
Why did it give us
those hallucinations?
Because it didn'’t!
Uh, yeah-huh.
Opal has unusual
temporal properties.
It preserves each head
in a time stasis bubble.
Ergo, licking those heads
actually sent us back in time
to their original
eras. Look!
ZOIDBERG:
Ugh!
Schlock and more schlock.
Psst. Is the coast clear?
Button your
yap, you mug.
I'’ve discovered a new means
of time travel.
I'’ll call it
the Farnsworth Effect!
Nice try,
but even this discovery won'’t
undo the treachery wrought
by your nefarious ancestor
David Farnsworth.
It will if we go back
in time and stop him!
[gasps]Oh!
Professor, no! You can'’t tongue
the father of our country!
[whoosh]
Where are we?
Also, when are we?
68th and Broadway,
Colonial Era.
[cow bell jingles,
cow lowing]
Rush hour.
By my calculations,
this head trip will last
at most 24 hours.
We need to stop that monster
David Farnsworth!
LEELA:
Look at the date
on this newspaper.
April 17, 1775.
Say, on this exact date,
the Continental Congress was
meeting secretly in New York.
Maybe they can help us.
But they could be
meeting anywhere.
What are we going to do,
search building to building?
PROFESSOR:
We'’ll start with that one.
Alexander Hamilton of New York,
how say you?
Nay!
John Hancock
and John Adams of Massachusetts?
Yea!Yea!
The yeas have it.
Our nation'’s official joke state
shall be New Jersey.
[knocking]
Uh-oh.
[munching, swallowing]
[guns cocking,
door squeaks open]
Ah, '’tis just our
new crock pot.
Watch it, wiggy.
I ain'’t no
stinking crock.
We'’ll see about that
in five hours.
Halt! From whence comest
thou, one-eyed maiden?
Uh... ever been to Peru?
Certainly not.
I'’m from Peru.
Clam up, founding fathers.
We need help
locating the treacherous forger
who forged this forgery.
[gasping]
My word.
If these enter circulation,
our economy will
be destroyed,
and with it, our
chance at independence.
Only one man
in the colonies
has a printing press
fine enough to make these.
Our good friend
Ben Franklin!
Uh-oh. Isn'’t Franklin
in Philadelphia?
When he'’s not in Charlotte
or Marybelle or Louisa.
[laughter]
I don'’t get it.
I'’m sure
no one'’s ever said this before,
but I must get to Philadelphia
as quickly as possible!
Oh! Why couldn'’t my
disgraced ancestor
have lived in
the NASCAR era?
[door squeaks open]
Dr. Franklin, your new
steam engine is here.
I ain'’t no stinking
steam engine!
[ding]Chicken'’s ready.
You may go,
Louisa.
Now I get it.
[vibrating]
Fascinating.
Be you man or machine?
Mostly machine. Might be
a couple of dead cats in there.
Dr. Franklin, with
all due respect
to the brilliant
inventor of the... stove,
I must speak with you.Hmm?
I'’m looking for the scoundrel
who made this.
Intricate filigree,
satanic symbols.
Looks like one of mine.
[gasps]
But no, this is a fake!
Duh. It says "Colony
of Maffachufetts."
[scoffs]
More like Taxachufetts.
[sighs]
That'’s just how we print "S"s,
you ftupid fhitheads.
Someone must have
used my press
while I was poking
around in Charlotte.
Let'’s ask my apprentice,
David Farnsworth.
[gasps]
Farnsworth?!
That'’s him!
Arm yourselves!
I call it
the Franklinator.
[door squeaks open, gasps]
[squeaking]
The apprentice'’s suite is empty!
He'’s gone!
Wait. What'’s that glistening
in the chamber pot?
Let'’s find out!
Bender, do you know
what a chamber pot is?
I don'’t know,
and I don'’t care.
A Massachusetts
halfpenny?
Probably fake, too.
There'’s one way to find out.
[all groaning in disgust]What?
Bender bit a poo penny.
Look, '’tis but worthless tin.
Where could Farnsworth have
minted such a high quality fake?
Not here. But, you know,
I have a friend in Boston
who'’s an expert silversmith.
They could be connected.
There'’s only like 40 people
who do anything around here.
But Boston'’s 300 miles away,
and Bender kicked
our horse to death.
We'’ll never
get there in time.
Unless you have another
invention up your sleeve.
[scoffs]
Hmm...
[thunder crashes, rain falling]
How is this going
to get us to Boston?
Ow!
[grumbling]
Stupid Franklin.
I will get you!
[grumbling]
Ah, that scrap metal
I ordered is here.
I'’m 40% scrap metal.[metallic clang]
Well, Ben Franklin, my
fellow son of liber...
teakettles.
Yes, I'’ve made some
new teakettles.
Perfect for
special occasions.
Like hanging King
George in effigy...
and "H" and "I" are monograms
you can put on those kettles.
What are you looking at,
you British bastards?
Paul, we talked
about this.
Mr. Revere, we'’re looking
for a counterfeiter
who minted these
smelly halfpennies.
His name is
David Farnsworth.
Farnsworth? I just hired him
for the fall candlestick rush.
He'’s in the foundry
this very moment.
[all gasp]
Everybody, take a Franklinator.
Aw, I got a chipmunk.
Hee-yah!
Uh, wha...?
David Farnsworth,
I presume?
[in cockney accent]:
I is Davy Farnsworth.
Foof. You'’re a disgrace
to the very name
[imitating David]
"Farnsworth."
Look out. He'’s got
a bezelling planisher.
That'’s right.
Who wants to be bezelled?
[both grunting]
[grunting]
You idiot.
I'’m not a cannon.
Huh. I guess I
am a cannon.
[groans]
Time to prune
the family tree.
Wha!
[all cheering]
Huzzah!
I'’ve saved the Farnsworth name.
[panting]
Urgent message
for Mr. Revere.
"Mr. Revere,
"pray do not
'’fhit'’ your pants.
"The British attack
has begun.
Cross the river and
watch for my signal."
I must ride.
[horse whinnies]
He has so much stuff.
He won'’t miss this.
Let'’s burn these counterfeits
and paddle the next swan boat
the hell out of Boston.
Here you go.Thanks.
Say, where did you
get that lantern?
From that old church
to the north.
They had two burning, so I
figured they wouldn'’t miss one.
"One if by land,
two if by sea."
The British are coming.
By land. By land.
Gotta treat this OCD.
Fry, you dope.
You'’ve really screwed
the grannie this time.
History needed
that second lantern.
We'’d better stop
Paul Revere before...
[in English accent]:
I guess everything worked out
jolly all right,
eh, governor?
[laughing]
[in English accent]: What'’s with
the fruity accent, ducky?
Bollocks, I got it, too.
[in English accent]: Where'’s all
the Presidents heads, then?
[in English accent]:
I say.
Appears we'’ve changed
history too much.
Disaster of nightmarish
proportions and whatnot.
Quite.
Where have you
blokes been?
You nearly missed elevenses.
Who'’s for tea
and shmavouries?
What in bloody hell'’s going
on around here, I says.
Indeed. What'’s become
of the dear old USA?
Beg pardon?
The Revolution?
1776 and what all?
Oh, the Colonial dustup.
Well, there'’s nothing
we Brits enjoy more
than a good documentary.
Turn on the tellyvisor,
Dr. Zoidsmythe.
I'’ll dial up the Beeb.
They'’ve always got
a nice docky-wocky on.
NARRATOR: The Vanquished Pride
of the Yankees,
or, America the Dutiful.
North America,
or West Britannia
as we now call it,
has been under British rule
for 1400 years,
all thanks to a nutter
known as "Wrong-Way Revere."
The British are coming
by land, by land.
[laughing goofily]
But we came by sea, we did.
Surprised the Yanks
at Lexington,
ending the rebellion
with nary a kipper scuffed.
Scuffed kippers, anyone?
Right kind of you, mum.
The humiliated conspirators
were forced to sign  the Declaration of Dependence,
proclaiming
British rule forever.
Meanwhile, a loyal Brit
by the name of David Farnsworth
tracked down the traitor
George Washington,
and bravely smothered him
with his wig.
[Washington gasping]
Oh, criminy.
In gratitude, King George
named Farnsworth a duke
and granted his family massive  land-holdings in the colonies.
Blimey. I'’ve never felt
so ashamed to be a Farnsworth.
Will my lord be returning
to his massive
land-holdings for luncheon?
Huh, wha?
[yawns]
I know we'’re
ladies-in-waiting,
but what are
we waiting for?
How should I know?
Just shut up and wait.
Say, how is it that we'’ve
got socialized medicine,
but me teeth
still look like this?.
Can'’t we just go back in time,
and set things right again?
Don'’t want to.
Rather nice, living under
the Crown and so forth.
Rather. Oh!
What'’s more, couldn'’t go back,
even if we wanted to.
No more crystalline opal left
in all the world,
don'’t you know.
My lord, the queen is here
for her weekly, er, visit.
The queen?
Sounds most satisfactory.
All of you, out.
Right then.
Let'’s go play some quoits,
whatever that is.
♪ ♪
Presenting the Queen of England,
America,
and two parking spaces in Tokyo.
Where'’s me consort at?
C-Consort?
That'’s right, love.
Fer centuries, the
Farnsworth gentlemen
has provided service
to the Queen.
Now, close your eyes
and think of England.
I say.
What'’s that in your crown?
You mean the
Andamooka Opal?
That'’s the most precious
gem in all the...
[clanging]
Yes.
Three rubbers on the hobb.
[Professor panting]
Stop him!
He crowned me in the knickers
and nicked me crown.
[all panting]
Freeze.
Or we'’ll be forced
to continue chasing you,
since we don'’t carry guns.
Indubitably.
[all panting]
We'’ve got to go back in time
and set things straight.
Hurry up and lick
Washington'’s head again.
We can'’t. There'’s
no George Washington
nor any other
presidents.
What about this bloke?
He'’s from Revolutionary times.
Farnsworth.
Hey, you'’re the plonkers
what candlesticked me.
Well, I showed you.
I killed George Washington,
and now I'’m married
to one of the Spice Girls.
Don'’t rightly know which one.
Bender, fetch me
that powdered opal.
[grunting]
It'’s time to restore dignity
to the Farnsworth name.
Ew!
There.
That time I left
both lanterns in place.
And I hit Farnsworth
much, much harder.
Perhaps too hard.
Look, all the presidents
are back.
Even John Tyler.
That'’s the first time
anyone'’s spoken
to me in 1,200 years.
Yes, from Chester A. Arthur
to Chester Z. Arthur,
they'’re all here.
Our republic
and the Farnsworth
family name are saved.
And no one will ever know.
[chuckling]
Yeah.