Fuck! We're gone a few days
and the Snyderverse people
took over.
Yeah! Screw the patriarchy!
And this car!
-Nora?
-Wait, Ivy?
[gasps] Oh, my God!
Where have you been?
Oh. Hey, Harley.
[singing in Italian]
Okay. What the fuck
is going on?
Nice of you two hos to finally
join us for the apocalypse.
Wait? It's already happened.
Oh! We'll just go back
in the time-sphere
and go back a week.
[both gasp]
[theme music playing]
[accordion music playing]
[grumbling]
Hey! Pasta-maker makers beware.
I have arrived!
Receptionisto!
I was on hold with you
for 94 hours
and after realizing
that seemed futile,
I came to speak with you
mano-a-mano.
[In Italian accent] Do you have
an appointimento?
No, I do not have appointmento.
I was stuck
in Homeland Security
for months.
Then in customs,
also for months.
Then my mask tubes
got tangled
in your olive branches
for uncountable hours.
[groans softly]
And now I will finally
complete my quest to win
my coworker's affections
by fixing the handle
of her boss' pasta maker.
That handle is discontinuato.
Discontinued! Unacceptable!
[sighs wearily]
What about in the back?
Sometimes a store
doesn't think
they have something.
Then they check in the back
and they're like,
"Well, there it is."
It is a-not in the back.
You do not understand.
My whole life,
I have existed in darkness,
hopeless that I would
find someone
who connects with me
on an emotional
and spiritual level.
Well, I have found her...
My lovely Nora.
But if I don't find
a new handle
for this pasta maker,
I will lose her.
Discontinuato.
Pasta pricks!
[disco music playing]
Marcos, you're the only
IRS auditor worth a damn!
Good luck
with the promotion, buddy.
You deserve it.
[belches] Ah!
Take that, suckas.
In other news,
Lex Luthor has announced
he's about to start repairing
the ozone layer
with the Earth Saver by Lex.
Whenever you're ready,
Mr. Luthor.
Jesus, Elvis,
Rihanna's baby.
And now, Lex Luthor.
When the pages of history
look back on today...
Oh! I'm too excited.
Let's go.
[laser whooshes]
-What did you do?
-Sir,
it appears our
maximum laser range
is 304cm short
of the Earth's atmosphere.
In English!
It's about 10ft short, sir.
[grunts]
[screams]
I will find you an even better
pasta maker handle.
[speaking in Italian accent]
Excuzi me-zee, Italian man.
Can you tell me
where I can find
the best pasta maker
in all of Italy?
[snoring]
These people
and their fucking naps!
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
Hola, bambinos.
It's a me, Bahn-io.
[in Italian]
[all laughing]
Indeed.
Where do I find
the best pasta maker
in all of Italy?
Eh, pasta maker.
Grazie, Mille!
Huh?
Damn you, street urchins!
[Bane grunting]
Every blister is worth it,
my sweet Nora!
[sighing] Nora!
Nora!
-[Lenny] Nora. Nora.
-[Nora laughs mischievously]
Hmm.
It's so much hotter
when someone's sleeping
in the same room.
How is she even comfortable?
Did someone say comfortable?
Ooh. Can't wait to get
my tongue stuck to that.
[both moan]
Actually, before we
get into it,
I need a bowl of pasta.
BRB.
[sputtering] Oh, yeah.
Yeah, me too.
It's always been
a dream of mine
to simultaneously explode
all the volcanoes on Earth.
Ivy's going to be so proud.
She recommended you.
What the fuck is going on here?
I was asked to help Lex with--
Can it, lava lips!
I wanna hear it from him.
Oh, I'm just borrowing
a low-level employee
to activate some volcanoes
around the world,
creating enough heat
to raise the ozone up...
Oh, I don't know,
ten-ish feet.
It doesn't matter why.
Seems like it does matter why.
This doesn't concern you, Nora.
Oh? A nefarious
business tycoon, comes
into the office on a Sunday
to take a
wet-behind-the-ears rube,
to help with
a personal project.
All my alarm bells
are going off, buster!
Oh, no! Am I in trouble?
I thought Ivy knew.
Is she gonna be mad at me or--
Why are you even here
on a Sunday?
I always work weekends.
Ugh! Go back to your nerd hole.
And put your headphones on.
It's about to get nasty
in here.
Not so fast!
Explain yourself.
I thought that she was
doing that press tour
for her line
of business corsets
with the Jons.
Ivy's not working
with the Jons anymore.
She blew them to smithereens,
you slippery son of a--
She did what?
God, you men!
You drain our titties
when you're baby boys
and now you're making us
run your companies?
Get out!
[grunting]
Knock, knock.
Hello?
[suspenseful music playing]
Um, mi scusi?
[groans]
Who stabs my weary heart?
[speaking Italian]
Apologies, Signora.
I wandered onto your property
on my botched search
for the best pasta maker
in all of Italy.
[speaking in Italian accent]
You have found her, beefy man.
A-ha!
Ivy, you'll never guess
what that twat Lex tried to do.
Okay, seriously, wake up.
Do you have toxic shock?
You've been sleeping
for, like, days.
-You're not Ivy!
-[groans]
Enough with
the wig shenanigans.
Ivy's not even there.
All right, Lexinators,
move in.
Aren't you worried
about Ivy?
No one's heard from her.
Yeah, feels like
a Monday problem.
Now, where were we?
-[both gasp]
-Duck!
Volcana, you perv!
What are you doing?
Recharging in the comfort
of Ivy's random hairs
and chip crumbs?
[guns cocking]
[Nora groans]
[Volcana] Unhand me!
Did someone change
the WiFi password?
[groaning]
-Ice!
-Fire!
[groans]
I thought I was
the only sucker
working on a Sunday.
No one has work-life
boundaries anymore.
We're being trolled
by a petty-ass bald himbo
who's trying to keep me
from getting laid!
Girl, you are messy.
Come on, Lenny.
Let's continue this in my car.
-[belches]
-Ew!
Grazie, Signora.
I will never forget
your act of
international kindness.
No freeloading.
You eat my parmesan,
you help in the kitchen, huh?
[whining] I need rest!
I'm afraid my body
will fail me!
Now is not the time for fear.
Fear comes-ah later.
After dessert?
Silencio! I ask the questions.
-You make-a the dough
or out you get-a.
-[groans]
Shit, shit, shit!
What the shit
are we gonna do?
Can't you use your powers
to explode us out of here?
I'm famously known for fires,
not explosions.
It's a subtle but very
important distinction.
[Lex on intercom]
Ivy's underlings,
you have one last chance
to hand over Volcana.
I wish Ivy were here.
Well, she's not!
And the line of succession
I just decided on
says I'm in charge.
[Lex] Nora,
I take your silence
as a refusal to hand over
the fire breather?
Uh-huh. That's right.
I've seen men like you
take young, nerdy women before.
Well, not on my watch!
Aw! Thank you, Nora.
Will someone put her
in the panic room already!
The LOD doesn't have
a panic room.
God, I can't deal
with all these personalities.
Don't worry, work fam.
Time for this shark to shine.
I'm gonna hack us out of here.
[exhilarating music playing]
Can you get into
Ivy's bank account?
I wanna know
what that bitch makes.
Quick. Someone get me something
with taurine in it.
I would not call it
love at first sight.
What I have with Nora
is much deeper.
Hey! We work with the hands,
not the mouth.
You are being
quite rough with me.
Oh! It is passion! It is life!
-Ow.
-Now, focus.
Okay, little egg. Crack!
[Bane grumbles]
Your eggs are faulty!
I will 'splode them all!
Argh!
[hen clucks]
Give to me a photo
of your beloved.
Now you try.
[groans softly] Okay.
But I will assuredly break her
like I have so many bodies
and spirits in my career.
Not if you break it for her.
[exclaims]
Think of this dough
as like a bosoms
of your Nora.
[chuckles nervously] Oh, my.
Uh, like... like this?
Perfecto.
Um, don't forget to play
with the nipples.
[chuckles softly] Oh, well.
Again. You must
do it yourself.
In my kitchen,
there is no rope!
[sighs wearily]
I can't!
You can! Look at our hands.
They are not so different.
Yes, each of yours is like
five little sausage,
stuck to a fresh ball
of mozzerella.
But they can still do
delicate work.
Hmm. Assembling my bombs
for 'splosions
has always required
a nimble touch, I suppose.
Yes!
Think of each fettuccine
as a, um,
'splosive of feelings
for your Nora.
Now, cut.
[Bane grunting]
Too thick! Again!
Nora! Nora! Nora! Nora!
[slurping]
[groaning] My dick's
gonna fall off
waiting for you.
Look, I took this job hoping
there'd be way more
villainous IT emergencies,
not just helping folks
do their timecard online.
Finally, this is my moment!
This is fascinating
watching you.
Hey! That's supposed to be
my sensual neck massage!
I'm trying to keep
my guy loose.
And I'm learning so much.
[mimicking gunshots]
I can't die watching
two men bond over tech.
Of course! The Imbigulator!
We can use this
to make the building bigger
and the armor will pop off.
No! Nora, I need this.
-It's my time to prove
I'm more than just a dad.
-[laptop chimes]
And... ooh, la, la!
I just got through
another firewall.
A few more minutes
and we are good, to--
Oh! I've been Imbigulated!
-I can't hack like this!
-Ah, crap. It's single use.
[rooster crows]
Wake up!
Time for mangia!
Oh, I love pasta.
Meele gratzis, Signora.
No! Not Signora.
You call me Mama.
Mama Nacaroni.
Like Mama... Macaroni?
Yes, my cousin's ristorante.
Our name is-a Nacaroni.
But they changed it
at Ellis Island.
This is the most delicious
pasta I have ever had.
Who made this?
You did.
What? When?
Il buffone , you are the
second greatest pasta maker
in all of Italy.
I am the pasta maker?
Mama, I may have been
born in a prison,
but I have been living
in a prison of my own
making,
the warden,
my self-doubt.
I have become the thing
that I sought!
Thank you, Mama.
[King Shark]
Will you look at these mitts?
How am I gonna to drive home?
Oh, fuck!
My babysitter must be
in triple overtime by now.
How many times have I asked you
not to mention children
in my presence?
[Lex] Enough with your
female antics!
It's time to...
turn up the heat.
[whooshes]
He said it like a pun,
but that's what he
literally did.
How embarrassing!
[chuckles softly]
[Lex] And I didn't mean
it as a pun.
It's a double entendre,
if anything!
But that's irrelevant
because I meant the turn on
the poison vapor.
[yelling] Where the fuck
is the poison vapor?
No, it's not in my car.
I thought it was in your car.
Well, go and get it!
Ugh! My pits are gushing.
I'll cool you down, baby.
Heat is my most
despised nemesis.
Ooh, yes. Ooh!
Do my elbows.
[moans]
[both moaning]
[exclaiming] Get me
out of here!
-[vapor whooshes]
-[Lex] Ah! There we go.
-You! Cover that vent.
-No can do.
It's too high up.
Why can't any of you just,
like, get big and tall
and be impervious to gas?
Can you at least
create an explosion
to get us out of here?
I can make you an iced coffee?
[groans softly] God!
Where's that 'splosions guy
when you need a 'splosion?
You mean Bane?
Oh, now I'm supposed to learn
everyone's names?
[scoffs] Okay.
[Bane humming]
Do you think you could part
with a wedge of parm
for my trip home, Mama?
Home?
Si, Mama.
I now return to Gotham
with all the secrets and wisdom
I learned
in our short, but meaningful
time together.
Hairy vaderchy!
-No.
-Huh?
Now, you will take over
my business
and be my heir.
But Mama,
you fixed my problems,
so I don't need you any--
[groans]
Madre di puttana!
You cannot
come to this country,
steal from us and then leave.
You're a cultural tourist!
What now?
You're gonna sell my story
to some asshole
at a streaming service.
Mama, let's be reasonable.
You think I would
teach you a craft I spent-a
my whole life perfecting
and expect nothing in return?
-[grunting]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[groans softly]
-[all coughing]
-[Nora] Okay,
if we're gonna die
under my leadership,
we're gonna do it looking
like fucking supermodels!
This is where I stash
all the hair products,
diet snacks,
and little pink guns
that brands send to Ivy
hoping to get her endorsement.
And it's also where I put
that volcano girl.
[all exclaiming] Oh, fuck!
Oh, thank, Mount Vesuvius!
Why'd you lock me in here?
I told you it wasn't
a panic room!
You're alive, aren't you?
Ooh, gas masks!
Ooh, gum!
[Volcana] This is literally
the most flammable closet
in all of Gotham.
Hairspray, gunpowder,
snacks made with
highly-combustible ingredients.
I'm lucky I didn't explode!
Explode, like an explosion?
-Yes.
-Hmm.
[Bane groaning]
What? No!
You will pay the price
for your insolence
with death.
Can't we sit and talk this out
over an aperitivo?
Mama! Not my fingers!
I need these
to pleasure Nora...
with my calligraphy!
And to continue working
as a semi-famous villain
in Gotham!
Wait. You are semi-famous?
Clayface? Hi.
It's... It's me, Bane.
No, Bane.
From 'sploding things?
Yes!
So, look. My former mentor
has me at knife point,
and she's demanding tickets
to your Vegas show.
-[softly] Front row.
-Front row, she says.
Um...
You want me
to head-butt Poison Ivy
on the Gotham News live
just to embarrass her?
But she's my Nora's boss...
You've got a deal.
Bravo, Il Buffone.
Ugh!
-Hairspray!
-Paint guns!
[Nora] Diet snacks!
I can carry so much stuff
with these big hands.
Look! I'm holdin' like
20 diet sodas.
Someone take a pic!
Might as well throw this
in there.
I don't know how to put it
back on the wall.
Wow, this is just like
Die Hard.
Oh, the over-referenced
action movie
that's been parodied
into oblivion?
Well, not today!
[Volcana retching]
You could have just asked me!
You, scorpion woman!
[screaming]
-[machine beeping]
-Will you look at that.
Mr. Luthor, an explosion
in Gotham imbigulated
the atmosphere
and pushed it 304cm...
I mean, 10ft higher.
We are now in range
to regenerate the ozone.
Smash that follow, Professor.
[sighing]
Farewell, little thief boy!
I am going home
to my dear Nora.
Ciao ciao, Toilet!
Ah! So bellissimo.
I now see the world
in the artistic way
the Italians do.
[fire crackling]
We did it, co-workers.
Pretty sure we all have
concussions,
but I slept great.
Should we get bagels?
We still have no idea
where Ivy is.
When's the swelling
gonna go down?
Tell me about it.
My balls are so blue.
Wait, guys...
[dramatic music playing]
Who turned off the sun?
My babies!
They need me!
Do you think Lex did this?
Who cares?
Let's find someplace private
before the world ends.
-Not now, I want free stuff!
-[groans]
Anyone want a laminator?
[Bane] Hey, Nora.
Mi amore!
'Splosions guy!
Where were you
when I needed you?
I was in Italia,
trying to replace the handle
of Ivy's pasta maker for you.
I failed.
But in my journey
of self-discovery,
I achieved something
far better.
Sono il pastaio!
I am the pasta maker!
Yeah, I had pasta for lunch.
[sighing in despair]
Hey, can you break
that window for me?
I want that beach umbrella.
Um...
But I thought you wanted pasta.
[siren blaring in the distance]
Who am I to question
my Nora's whims!
Nice of you two hos to finally
join us for the apocalypse.
Wait? It's already happened.
Oh! We'll just go back
in the Time Sphere
and go back a week.
[both gasp]
Oop! My bad.
I meant to hit
that fancy diaper store
I've been afraid to go in.
[chuckles softly]
These hands have no precision.
Keep up, 'Splosions Guy.
[woman reporter on TV]
The Earth Saver by Lex
is up and running,
thickening the ozone.
But Gotham wonders,
is it too thick?
It seems as if Lex
has blocked out the sun
and, even worse,
he has refused our request
for comment.
-[whooshing]
-Halt, looters!
[thuds]
Oh, no. The sun!
Stay away! Nobody touch me!
Where's the nearest
tanning salon?
Do we still have those?
As a culture?
Oh, my God.
Did Lex do all this
just fuck Superman?
Eh, I've done worse
to fuck less,
but still,
that is some petty shit.
[theme music playing]